# Dede Badru

Software Engineer

Jl. Tegal Kawung, Kota Cimahi - 40511

dede.badrujaman@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/dedebadru

#### **OBJECTIVE**

I am a software engineer. I have worked for almost 8 years at different companies. My current position is product engineer on WIP that owns the product ATOZPAY as an ewallet application and ATOZGO for delivery service application, at WIP I have responsibility to develop and maintain the product (ATOZPAY & ATOZGO).

### **EDUCATION**

- Universitas Nurtanio Bandung Teknik Informatika
- SMK Negeri 11 Bandung Rekayasa Perangkat Lunak

#### RELATED EXPERIENCES

**Product Engineer,** Weyland Indonesia Perkasa (2017 - Present)

Frontend Developer, Appschef (2016 - 2017)

**Developer, Walden Global Services (2013 - 2016)** 

## **RELATED SKILL**

Framework Programming
Javascript
Database engine
Ruby on Rails, and Laravel
Vuejs, Angular, and Jquery
MySQL, and postgreSQL

• Subversion : Git

• Environments Dev : Vagrant, Docker

• Cloud : AWS, and Digital Ocean

• Operating system : UNIX